[
    {
        "question": "What is the HTML tag under which one can write the JavaScript code?",
        "options": [
            " <javascript>",
            "<scripted>",
            "<script>",
            "<js>"
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 2
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax to display “GeeksforGeeks” in an alert box using JavaScript?",
        "options": [
            "alertbox(“GeeksforGeeks”);",
            "msg(“GeeksforGeeks”)",
            "msgbox(“GeeksforGeeks”)",
            "alert(“GeeksforGeeks”)"
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called “geek.js”?",
        "options": [
            "<script src=”geek.js”>",
            "<script href=”geek.js”>",
            "<script ref=”geek.js”>",
            "<script name=”geek.js”>"
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a reserved word in JavaScript?",
        "options": [
            "interface",
            "throws",
            "program",
            "short"
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the syntax for creating a function in JavaScript named as Geekfunc?",
        "options": [
            "function = Geekfunc()",
            "function Geekfunc()",
            "function := Geekfunc()",
            "function : Geekfunc()"
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "How is the function called in JavaScript?",
        "options": [
            "call Geekfunc()",
            "call function GeekFunc()",
            "Geekfunc()",
            "function Geekfunc()"
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the correct syntax for adding comments in JavaScript?",
        "options": [
            "<!–This is a comment–&gt",
            "//This is a comment",
            "–This is a comment",
            "**This is a comment**"
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the JavaScript syntax for printing values in Console?",
        "options": [
            "print(5)",
            "console.log(5)",
            "console.print(5)",
            "print.console(5)"
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What will be the command to print the number of characters in the string “GeeksforGeeks”?",
        "options": [
            "document.write(“GeeksforGeeks”.len);",
            "document.write(sizeof(“GeeksforGeeks”));",
            "document.write(“GeeksforGeeks”.length)",
            "document.write(lenof(“GeeksforGeeks”));"
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the method in JavaScript used to remove the whitespace at the beginning and end of any string ?",
        "options": [
            "strip()",
            "trim()",
            "stripped()",
            "trimmed()"
        ],
        "type": "radio",
        "userResponse": "",
        "answer": 1
    }
]